Studer, Norman; Papers apap116
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1817-1999; Undated; 9; 3.62 cubic ft.
  - Death of a Valley by Dorothea Lange and Pickle Jones, 1960 (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - Delaware County, Undated (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - De Nio, Pierre and Mary, 1958-1959; 1963; Undated (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Downsville News Clips, 1945; 1948 (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Dutchess County, New York, 1964; Undated (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - "Education and Community," by Fred Newmann and Donald Oliver, 1966 (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Education Bibliography, Undated (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Emotion and the Education Process, Undated (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Ernie Sager and the Traveling Show, Undated (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Example of Folklore, Undated (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - "The Experience of Knowledge," by John F. Gardner, 1972 (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Farming, 1950 (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Five Papers in Education, 1949; 1953; Undated (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - Flax Processing, 1959; Undated (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - The Folk Dancer, 1945 (Box 1 (9-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Folkdance - Folksong with Karl Finger, 1977-1978; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Folklore Notes and Clippings, 1959; 1975; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Fontier, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - General Folklore Meetings and Notes, 1948; 1960; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - George Edwards: Catskill Folksinger, Marilyn Kimball Thesis, Chapters 1-3, 1966 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - George Edwards: Catskill Folksinger, Marilyn Kimball Thesis, Chapters 4-6, 1966 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - George Edwards: Catskill Folksinger, Marilyn Kimball Thesis, Postscript, Bibliography and Appendices, 1966 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Greene County, 1963; 1971; 1973-1974; 1976; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Hallenbeck, Lew, 1948 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Haufrecht, Herbert, 1980 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Huckleberry Bill, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - "The Hudson and the Rhine," by George William Curtis, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Hudson River Sloop Clearwater, 1968-1969; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - "In the Olden Days," Social Studies Project Compiled by Joan Levine's Students with the Help of Norman Studer, 1976-1977 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - "Intellectual Education," by David Mallery, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - James Alexander, Weaver, 1956 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Jeffersonian Movement, 1958; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - John Burroughs, 1948; 1954 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - "Johnny Appleseed, Jr." by Pete Seeger, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Journal of American Folklore, 1959 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Kingston, New York History, 1952; 1961-1962 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - "The Knickerbocker Line", Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Landmarks, 1953; 1962; 1968 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Langston Hughes, 1967 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - "Leather Breeches", 1939 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Leland Teich, 1978; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - "A Letter," by David Taylor, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Man: A Course of Study, 1970; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Map of Historic Hurley, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 12)
  - Materials about Norman Studer, Grant Rogers, Herbert Haufrecht, Mike Todd from Wilma Studer Porter, 1999 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Mathew Lyon, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 30-33)
  - "Maxcy Gregg" by Robert Krick, 1973 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Mathew Lyon, 1975; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - "Merry Ditties: A Collection of Delectable Songs," Compiled, Edited and Arranged by Norman Cazden, 1955 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 36)
  - Mexican Folk Art, 1925-1927; 1933; 1936; 1941; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 37)
  - Mike Todd, 1940; 1954; 1960; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 38)
  - Mileage Fact Sheet of the Appalachian Trail, 1978 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 39)
  - Mill House, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 40)
  - Mining, 1964; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 41)
  - "Music of the Catskills," by Herbert Haufrecht and Norman Cazden, 1948 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 42)
  - Nat Turner, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 43)
  - Native Americans, 1961; 1969 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 44)
  - "New Approaches in Education," by David Malley, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 45)
  - New Hampshire Patriot Issue, 1817 (Oversized 1, Folder 13)
  - New Paltz Center for Catskill Mountain and Hudson River Studies, 1974-1975; 1977; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 46)
  - New York City Neighborhood Survey, 1978 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 47)
  - New York City Water Supply, 1947; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 48)
  - The New Student, 1924-1927 (Oversized 3)
  - "A Note on Folklore" by Constance Rourke, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 49)
  - Notebook, 1977; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 50)
  - Notes on Catskill History, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 51)
  - "The Old Country Stove," by Janet MacFarlane, 1948 (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 52)
  - Old Forge, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 53)
  - Olney Smith, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 54)
  - Oral History, Etson Von Wagoner, 1944; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 55)
  - Oral History, Interview with William Vandemark, Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 56)
  - Oral History, Mrs. Celian Kelder, 1953; Undated (Box 2 (9-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Oral History, Notes on Visit to Many Jane Shaver, 1948 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Oral History, "Raising the Mill," D.C McLaughlin, Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Oral History, Recollections of Verney Falls, Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Orange County, NY, 1954; 1961; Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Palisades, 1969 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Parson Jonathan Fisher, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - "The Passing Parade," by G. Edwards, 1956 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - People's Songs, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Pepacton Reservoir, the Human Host, 1948-1954; Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Pete Markle, Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Physiographic Diagram of the New York Region, Undated (Oversized 1, Folder 14)
  - The Pioneer, Livingston Manor Central School, Featuring New York History and Culture, 1939 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Pioneer Woman, 1939 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Poems and Prose from Mrs. Thelma Patel's Class, 1972; Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - "Politics of the Attack on Black Studies," by Robert Allen, 1974 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Prattsville and Zadock Pratt, 1948; 1957; 1968-1969 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Private Education, 1968-1969; 1971; Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - "Proclaim Liberty Unto All the Land," Brief Biography of Sojourner Truth, Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Progressive Education, 1952 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Purposes and Objectives of a Proposed Applied Folklore Center in New York City, 1960 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Quarles Colonial Home Arts Festival, Project of Joan Studer, 1976 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Queens Then and Now Exhibit, 1975-1976 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Rafting on the Delaware, 1945; 1950; 1953; Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Railway Electrification in Japan, Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Red Thunder Cloud, 1971; 1974; 1983; 1996; Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Restoration of Richmond Town, 1961 (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - "Reorientation in Education", Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Sheep Industry, Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Sholem Settlement, Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Sketches, Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Sleepy Hollow and Tarrytown, Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Social Studies Curriculum, 1974; Undated (Box 3 (9-Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Sojourner Truth and Hurley, New York, 1968; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Sojourner Truth Library Dedication, 1971; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Sojourner Truth Memorial Fund, 1970-1971; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - "Songmaker of the Catskills: Grant Rogers", 1965 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Songs, 1942; 1944; 1946; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Songs Collected and Arranged by Herbert Haufrecht, 1943; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Spring Folk Festival, 1977 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - The Spy House, Hurley, New York, Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Squire Elwyn Davis, 1960; 1972; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Stamps, New York Theme, Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Stoney and Sparrow Troubadours of the Hudson Valley and Catskill Mountains, Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - "Stony Hollow," Norman Cazden Scores, 1949 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Sunnyside, Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Sunnyside and Woodside Histories, 1976; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Symposium on the Hudson River School of Art, 1973 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Temporary Commission to Study the Catskills, 1971; 1973-1974; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - "Theory for American Folklore," by Richard Dorson, Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Tignish Arts Foundation, 1965-1966; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - "The True Moral and Diverting Tale of the Cardiff Giant,", 1948 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - Van de Bogart, Aron, 1945-1946; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Varieties of Folklore, Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Vermont, Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Vision and Visual Thinking, 1966; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - "Vitality of Tradition and Local Songs," by Herbert Halpert, Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Walt Whitman House, Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Water Conservation, 1959; Undated (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - The Water Supply of the City of New York, 1947 (Box 4 (9-Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - West Shokan Lake, 1960; 1974 (Box 5 (9-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Walking Tours of the Museum of the City of New York, Undated (Box 5 (9-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Water Shortage, 1949; Undated (Box 5 (9-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - "When His Own Came Back," by Edward Eugene Ragna, Undated (Box 5 (9-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Wild Life and Nature, 1962; 1965-1966; Undated (Box 5 (9-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - "Woodland Serenade," by Herbert Haufrecht, 1956 (Box 5 (9-Subject Files), Folder 6)